Guide to the New York University Collection of Papyri, Ostraka, and Cuneiform Tablets MSS.559
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I. Papyri Fragments, 55 Linear Feet in 44 small flat boxes and 2 oversize flat boxes
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0802.02, cuid31624; 1 fragment 02.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0802.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0803, cuid31625; 1 fragment 08.0 x 09.0 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0803)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0804, cuid31626; 1 fragment 06.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0804)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0805, cuid31627; 1 fragment 05.5 x 11.0 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0805)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0806, cuid31628; 1 fragment 07.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0806)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0807, cuid31629; 1 fragment 03.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0807)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0808, cuid31630; 1 fragment 03.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0808)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0809, cuid31631; 1 fragment 02.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0809)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0810, cuid31632; 1 fragment 03.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0810)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0811, cuid31633; 1 fragment 05.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0811)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0812, cuid31634; 1 fragment 03.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0812)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0813, cuid31635; 1 fragment 01.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0813)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0814, cuid31636; 1 fragment 08.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0814)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0815, cuid31637; 1 fragment 05.5 x 12.0 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0815)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0816, cuid31638; 1 fragment 15.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0816)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0817, cuid31639; 1 fragment 02.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0817)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0818, cuid31640; 1 fragment 04.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0818)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0819, cuid31641; 1 fragment 05.0 x 08.5 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0819)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0820, cuid31642; 1 fragment 04.0 x 12.0 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0820)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0821, cuid31643; 1 fragment 14.0 x 07.5 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0821)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0822, cuid31644; 1 fragment 01.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0822)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0823, cuid31645; 1 fragment 04.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0823)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0824, cuid31646; 1 fragment 07.0 x 11.5 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0824)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0825, cuid31647; 1 fragment 02.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0825)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0826.01, cuid31648; 1 fragment 01.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0826.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0826.02, cuid31649; 1 fragment 00.5 x 00.3 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0826.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0827, cuid31650; 1 fragment 18.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0827)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0828, cuid31651; 1 fragment 06.5 x 07.0 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0828)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0829, cuid31652; 1 fragment 03.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0829)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0830, cuid31653; 1 fragment 03.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0830)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0831, cuid31654; 1 fragment 05.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0831)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0832, cuid31655; 1 fragment 06.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0832)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0833, cuid31656; 1 fragment 02.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0833)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0834, cuid31657; 1 fragment 03.0 x 07.5 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0834)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0835, cuid31658; 1 fragment 04.5 x 13.0 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0835)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0836, cuid31659; 1 fragment 06.5 x 05.5 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0836)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0837, cuid31660; 1 fragment 01.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0837)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0838, cuid31661; 1 fragment 03.5 x 05.5 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0838)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0839, cuid31662; 1 fragment 08.0 x 11.0 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0839)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0840, cuid31663; 1 fragment 03.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0840)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0841, cuid31664; 1 fragment 01.5 x 01.0 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0841)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0842, cuid31665; 1 fragment 01.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0842)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0843, cuid31666; 1 fragment 05.0 x 09.5 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0843)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0844, cuid31667; 1 fragment 04.5 x 01.5 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0844)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0845, cuid31668; 1 fragment 03.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0845)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0846, cuid31669; 1 fragment 01.5 x 07.5 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0846)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0847, cuid31670; 1 fragment 01.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0847)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0848, cuid31671; 1 fragment 01.0 x 02.5 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0848)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0849, cuid31672; 1 fragment 02.5 x 02.5 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0849)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0850, cuid31673; 1 fragment 02.5 x 02.5 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0850)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0851, cuid31674; 1 fragment 02.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0851)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0852, cuid31675; 1 fragment 04.5 x 02.5 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0852)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0853, cuid31676; 1 fragment 01.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0853)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0854, cuid31677; 1 fragment 06.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0854)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0855, cuid31678; 1 fragment 04.5 x 07.5 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0855)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0857, cuid31679; 1 fragment 01.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0857)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0859, cuid31680; 1 fragment 04.0 x 12.5 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0859)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0860, cuid31681; 1 fragment 10.0 x 17.5 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0860)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0861, cuid31682; 1 fragment 11.5 x 08.0 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0861)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0862, cuid31683; 1 fragment 06.0 x 07.5 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0862)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0863, cuid31684; 1 fragment 04.5 x 07.0 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0863)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0864, cuid31685; 1 fragment 09.0 x 08.5 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0864)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0865, cuid31686; 1 fragment 06.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0865)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0866, cuid31687; 1 fragment 02.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0866)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0867, cuid31688; 1 fragment 02.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0867)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0868, cuid31689; 1 fragment 00.5 x 01.0 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0868)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0869, cuid31690; 1 fragment 00.5 x 01.0 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0869)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0870, cuid31691; 1 fragment 07.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0870)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0871, cuid31692; 1 fragment 05.0 x 12.5 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0871)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0872, cuid31693; 1 fragment 08.5 x 10.5 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0872)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0873, cuid31694; 1 fragment 04.0 x 08.5 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0873)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0874, cuid31695; 1 fragment 06.5 x 07.0 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0874)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0875, cuid31696; 1 fragment 15.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0875)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0876, cuid31697; 1 fragment 04.5 x 08.0 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0876)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0877, cuid31698; 1 fragment 16.0 x 11.0 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0877)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0878, cuid31699; 1 fragment 01.5 x 01.0 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0878)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0879, cuid31700; 1 fragment 07.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0879)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0880, cuid31701; 1 fragment 02.5 x 09.0 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0880)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0881, cuid31702; 1 fragment 10.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0881)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0882, cuid31703; 1 fragment 01.5 x 11.0 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0882)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0883, cuid31704; 1 fragment 04.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0883)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0884, cuid31705; 1 fragment 04.5 x 10.0 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0884)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0885, cuid31706; 1 fragment 09.5 x 10.5 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0885)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0886, cuid31707; 1 fragment 02.5 x 04.5 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0886)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0887, cuid31708; 1 fragment 02.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0887)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0888, cuid31709; 1 fragment 07.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0888)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0889, cuid31710; 1 fragment 03.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0889)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0890, cuid31711; 1 fragment 01.5 x 02.5 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0890)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0891, cuid31712; 1 fragment 02.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0891)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0892, cuid31713; 1 fragment 04.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0892)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0893, cuid31714; 1 fragment 03.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0893)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0894, cuid31715; 1 fragment 02.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0894)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0895, cuid31716; 1 fragment 03.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0895)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0896, cuid31717; 1 fragment 04.0 x 12.0 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0896)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0897, cuid31718; 1 fragment 06.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0897)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0898, cuid31719; 1 fragment 04.0 x 10.0 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0898)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0899, cuid31720; 1 fragment 05.0 x 02.5 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0899)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0900, cuid31721; 1 fragment 03.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0900)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0901, cuid31722; 1 fragment 18.0 x 09.0 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0901)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0902, cuid31723; 1 fragment 04.5 x 09.0 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0902)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0903, cuid31724; 1 fragment 08.0 x 06.5 cm (Box 21, Item P.NYU inv 0903)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0904, cuid31725; 1 fragment 05.5 x 14.0 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0904)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0905, cuid31726; 1 fragment 05.5 x 12.0 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0905)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0906, cuid31727; 1 fragment 07.0 x 09.0 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0906)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0907, cuid31728; 1 fragment 01.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0907)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0908, cuid31729; 1 fragment 02.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0908)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0909, cuid31730; 1 fragment 03.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0909)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0910, cuid31731; 1 fragment 03.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0910)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0911, cuid31732; 1 fragment 03.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0911)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0912, cuid31733; 1 fragment 03.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0912)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0913, cuid31734; 1 fragment 02.5 x 01.5 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0913)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0914, cuid31735; 1 fragment 07.5 x 04.5 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0914)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0915, cuid31736; 1 fragment 08.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0915)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0916, cuid31737; 1 fragment 07.5 x 15.0 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0916)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0917, cuid31738; 1 fragment 08.0 x 07.5 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0917)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0918, cuid31739; 1 fragment 09.5 x 09.0 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0918)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0919, cuid31740; 1 fragment 04.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0919)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0920, cuid31741; 1 fragment 03.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0920)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0921, cuid31742; 1 fragment 02.0 x 02.5 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0921)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0922, cuid31743; 1 fragment 04.5 x 04.5 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0922)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0923, cuid31744; 1 fragment 01.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0923)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0924, cuid31745; 1 fragment 02.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0924)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0925, cuid31746; 1 fragment 02.0 x 01.0 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0925)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0926, cuid31747; 1 fragment 00.5 x 00.3 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0926)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0927, cuid31748; 1 fragment 01.5 x 00.5 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0927)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0928, cuid31749; 1 fragment 01.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0928)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0929, cuid31750; 1 fragment 01.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0929)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0930, cuid31751; 1 fragment 03.5 x 15.0 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0930)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0931, cuid31752; 1 fragment 05.5 x 09.5 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0931)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0932, cuid31753; 1 fragment 04.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0932)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0933, cuid31754; 1 fragment 04.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0933)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0934, cuid31755; 1 fragment 03.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0934)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0935, cuid31756; 1 fragment 01.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0935)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0936, cuid31757; 1 fragment 02.5 x 08.5 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0936)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0937, cuid31758; 1 fragment 04.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0937)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0938, cuid31759; 1 fragment 07.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0938)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0939, cuid31760; 1 fragment 07.5 x 04.5 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0939)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0940, cuid31761; 1 fragment 04.5 x 01.0 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0940)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0941, cuid31762; 1 fragment 02.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0941)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0942, cuid31763; 1 fragment 02.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0942)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0943, cuid31764; 1 fragment 06.0 x 09.5 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0943)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0944, cuid31765; 1 fragment 09.5 x 09.5 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0944)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0945, cuid31766; 1 fragment 06.0 x 10.5 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0945)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0946, cuid31767; 1 fragment 10.5 x 11.0 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0946)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0947, cuid31768; 1 fragment 01.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0947)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0948, cuid31769; 1 fragment 02.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0948)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0949, cuid31770; 1 fragment 01.5 x 01.0 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0949)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0950, cuid31771; 1 fragment 01.5 x 01.0 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0950)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0951, cuid31772; 1 fragment 01.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0951)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0952, cuid31773; 1 fragment 02.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0952)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0953, cuid31774; 1 fragment 02.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0953)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0954, cuid31775; 1 fragment 04.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0954)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0955, cuid31776; 1 fragment 02.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0955)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0956, cuid31777; 1 fragment 02.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0956)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0957, cuid31778; 1 fragment 03.5 x 01.0 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0957)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0958, cuid31779; 1 fragment 04.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0958)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0959, cuid31780; 1 fragment 05.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0959)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0960, cuid31781; 1 fragment 04.5 x 07.0 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0960)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0961, cuid31782; 1 fragment 03.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0961)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0962, cuid31783; 1 fragment 05.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0962)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0963, cuid31784; 1 fragment 05.0 x 12.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0963)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0964, cuid31785; 1 fragment 03.5 x 11.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0964)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0965, cuid31786; 1 fragment 07.5 x 10.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0965)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0966, cuid31787; 1 fragment 06.5 x 15.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0966)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0967, cuid31788; 1 fragment 13.5 x 11.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0967)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0968, cuid31789; 1 fragment 06.0 x 19.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0968)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0969, cuid31790; 1 fragment 01.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0969)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0970, cuid31791; 1 fragment 08.0 x 21.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0970)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0971, cuid31792; 1 fragment 08.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0971)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0972, cuid31793; 1 fragment 08.5 x 10.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0972)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0973, cuid31794; 1 fragment 05.5 x 08.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0973)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0974, cuid31795; 1 fragment 01.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0974)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0975, cuid31796; 1 fragment 15.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0975)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0976, cuid31797; 1 fragment 08.5 x 09.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0976)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0977, cuid31798; 1 fragment 06.0 x 08.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0977)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0978, cuid31799; 1 fragment 03.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0978)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0979, cuid31800; 1 fragment 08.0 x 06.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0979)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0980, cuid31801; 1 fragment 05.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0980)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0981, cuid31802; 1 fragment 01.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0981)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0982, cuid31803; 1 fragment 02.5 x 04.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0982)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0983, cuid31804; 1 fragment 02.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0983)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0984.01, cuid31805; 1 fragment 02.0 x 00.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0984.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0984.02, cuid31806; 1 fragment 00.5 x 02.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0984.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0984.03, cuid31807; 1 fragment 01.5 x 02.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0984.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0985, cuid31808; 1 fragment 01.5 x 01.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0985)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0986, cuid31809; 1 fragment 31.5 x 07.5 cm (Box 40, Item P.NYU inv 0986)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0987, cuid31810; 1 fragment 13.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0987)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0988, cuid31811; 1 fragment 06.0 x 10.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0988)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0989, cuid31812; 1 fragment 03.0 x 06.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0989)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0990, cuid31813; 1 fragment 01.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0990)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0991, cuid31814; 1 fragment 01.0 x 01.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0991)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0992, cuid31815; 1 fragment 09.5 x 16.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0992)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0993, cuid31816; 1 fragment 04.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0993)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0994, cuid31817; 1 fragment 05.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0994)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0995, cuid31818; 1 fragment 06.5 x 04.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0995)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0996, cuid31819; 1 fragment 02.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0996)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0997, cuid31820; 1 fragment 12.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0997)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0998, cuid31821; 1 fragment 03.0 x 08.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0998)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1000, cuid31822; 1 fragment 04.5 x 08.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1000)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1001, cuid31823; 1 fragment 03.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1001)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1002, cuid31824; 1 fragment 12.0 x 07.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1002)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1003, cuid31825; 1 fragment 06.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1003)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1004, cuid31826; 1 fragment 07.5 x 14.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1004)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1005, cuid31827; 1 fragment 05.0 x 06.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1005)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1006, cuid31828; 1 fragment 03.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1006)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1007, cuid31829; 1 fragment 06.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1007)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1008, cuid31830; 1 fragment 02.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1008)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1009, cuid31831; 1 fragment 06.0 x 17.0 cm (Box 40, Item P.NYU inv 1009)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1010, cuid31832; 1 fragment 02.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1010)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1011, cuid31833; 1 fragment 06.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1011)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1012, cuid31834; 1 fragment 08.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1012)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1013, cuid31835; 1 fragment 03.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1013)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1014, cuid31836; 1 fragment 06.0 x 09.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1014)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1015, cuid31837; 1 fragment 18.0 x 08.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1015)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1016, cuid31838; 1 fragment 01.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1016)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1018, cuid31839; 1 fragment 11.0 x 02.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1018)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1019, cuid31840; 1 fragment 04.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1019)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1020, cuid31841; 1 fragment 03.0 x 07.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1020)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1021, cuid31842; 1 fragment 06.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1021)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1022, cuid31843; 1 fragment 03.0 x 08.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1022)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1023, cuid31844; 1 fragment 07.5 x 08.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1023)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1024, cuid31845; 1 fragment 03.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1024)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1025, cuid31846; 1 fragment 07.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1025)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1026, cuid31847; 1 fragment 02.5 x 07.5 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1026)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1027, cuid31848; 1 fragment 18.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1027)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1028.01, cuid31849; 1 fragment 06.0 x 07.5 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1028.01)